[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
(Leonard:)Oh, Howard's losing it.
(Leonard:)Check out his latest Twitters.
"I'm at the bottom of a black hole
staring into the abyss.
(Leonard:)My life is meaningless.
My future is without hope."
(Raj:)Why don't we take him
to see the Blue Man Group?
(Leonard:)You think that'd help?
(Raj:)USA Today calls them
"Exuberant fun for the whole family."
(Leonard:)I don't know. Howard isn't really
the "family fun" kind of guy.
(Raj:)It's too bad he wasn't here
for that hooker.
She's exactly his type:
(Raj:)A hooker.
(Raj:)You know, I bet if we hired her,
that would cheer him up.
(Leonard:)We're not going to get
Wolowitz a hooker.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
"I'm so lonely and horny...
(Raj(reading Howard's twitter):)...I may open this $20 jar of peanuts
and end it all."
I suppose it wouldn't hurt
to get an estimate.